<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>r3vit Personal Website</title>
    <link>https://r3vit.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on r3vit Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:01:42 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://r3vit.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Glass Week 2023 Map</title>
      <link>https://r3vit.github.io/posts/glass-week-2023-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 18:01:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r3vit.github.io/posts/glass-week-2023-map/</guid>
      <description>Glass Week 2023 From 2017 onwards, Venice, the illustrious city of Italy renowned for over a millennium for its beautiful art of glassmaking, has been host to an annual international celebration known as &amp;ldquo;The Venice Glass Week.&amp;rdquo;
This festival was founded with a noble purpose: to commemorate, uphold, and propagate the cherished tradition of glass craftsmanship, which has not only manifested as an artistic expression but has also played a pivotal role in the economic fabric of city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pause</title>
      <link>https://r3vit.github.io/posts/pause/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 05:12:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r3vit.github.io/posts/pause/</guid>
      <description>Pause One post per week.
Exploring new things (AI), funny things (card and game generation), serious things (software architecture) and things I recently falled in love (glass).
Good intentions for the new year lasted 3 weeks :)
This post it&amp;rsquo;s more like an apology than a real update.
People First Something that I wrote (and how I wrote it) hurt people that I care a lot about. I removed the posts for now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sugar Stained Glass</title>
      <link>https://r3vit.github.io/posts/sugar-stained-glass/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 12:01:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r3vit.github.io/posts/sugar-stained-glass/</guid>
      <description>Sugar Stained Glass Kitchen experiments are a great way to tap into your inner scientist.
One particularly fascinating experiment is creating fake glass using sugar.
What happen when you want to mix two complete different worlds like cooking and glass making?
The answer is: something sweet and imperfect, like all the good human things in this world!
The goal is not to create some &amp;ldquo;fake glass pieces for halloween cupcakes&amp;rdquo; but trying to recreate some dust-catching stained glass projects in the baking world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quasi estranei game</title>
      <link>https://r3vit.github.io/posts/quasi-estranei-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 11:01:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r3vit.github.io/posts/quasi-estranei-game/</guid>
      <description>Quasi estranei game It was Thursday evening when discovered from the web this card game:
WE ARE NOT REALLY STRANGERS
What&amp;rsquo;s the purpose of that game?
From their official website:
We&amp;rsquo;re Not Really Strangers is a purpose driven card game and movement all about empowering meaningful connections. Three carefully crafted levels of questions and wildcards that allow you to deepen your existing relationships and create new ones.
Seems interesting! How it&amp;rsquo;s made?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://r3vit.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 16:15:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r3vit.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About me Hi! 👋
I&amp;rsquo;m an Æternal student.
r3vit is the nickname used by a passionate Gopher, developer and
technology experimentalist called Marco.
From technologies to programming languages, from failures to successes, I love
working on projects that bring solutions to small and big problems.
I studied Computer Science and right now trying to work on meaningfull R&amp;amp;D projects for a company called Alkemy.
I believe in Open Source and try to follow the motto: &amp;ldquo;Changing the world, one bit at a time&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Refactoring</title>
      <link>https://r3vit.github.io/posts/website-refactoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 09:48:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://r3vit.github.io/posts/website-refactoring/</guid>
      <description>r3v.it refactoring Hello world!
This is only an example of blog post for website refactoring.
In this website I&amp;rsquo;ll put writings about things that I like and love.
You will not find the answers of you most deep questions, the the &amp;ldquo;best resources&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;exciting posts&amp;rdquo;.
Just some thoughts and hopes.
It&amp;rsquo;s not perfect, but it&amp;rsquo;s mine.
This is my brain
And it&amp;rsquo;s fine
It&amp;rsquo;s where I spend a vast majority of my time</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
